Bernard L. Fontana Papers 1832-2000 (bulk 1956-1985)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Writings
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts
    - Biography of a Desert Church., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Blood Groups in the American Southwest., undated; 1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Breaking the Ring – Political Evolution in Apache County., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Campfires on Desert and Lava., 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chas F. Lummis., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Continuity of European Settlement in Southern Arizona., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Death and Survival in the Sonoran Desert., 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Drawing the Line., 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Early Efforts for Statehood., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Entrada – Production., 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Entrada – Promotion., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Entrada – Review., 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Ethnobotany of the Saguaro., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Evaluating Religious Services., undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Geronimo., 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Gifts to Saints (1 of 2)., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Gifts to Saints (2 of 2)., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - The Great Encounter., undated; 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - The Green Dog., 1961 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - The Heroes of Gallo Isle., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Indians of Arizona (1 of 2)., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Indians of Arizona (2 of 2)., 1995 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Inventing the Southwest., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - John A. Jacobsen’s Southwest Diary., 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Jose Lewis Brennan., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Kit Carson’s Arizona., 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - The Kiva., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Lecture on Learning., 1985 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Linguistic Dowsing., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - The Man California Forgot., undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Massacre on the Gila – Published Sources., undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Massacre on the Gila – Published Sources., 1949-1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Massacre on the Gila – Reviews., 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Milagros Study., 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Mission San Xavier del Bac – The West Chapel., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The New Mission Cult in Southern California., undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Of Earth and Little Rain – Press Reprint., 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Of Earth and Little Rain – Response Letters., 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - On Paul Ezell., undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Onza., 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Painting Papago Pottery., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - The Papago Indians – Edited Copy (1 of 2)., undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Papago Indians – Edited Copy (2 of 2)., undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Papago Indians – Finished Copy., undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Papago Potter: Listiana Francisco., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Pilgrimage to Magdalena., undated; 1981-1993 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Pilgrimage to San Xavier., 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Pithouse to Skyscraper., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Preserving a Monument., 1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Pimería Alta – Correspondence., 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Pimería Alta – A Guide to Pimería Alta Draft., 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Pimería Alta – Land of the Papagos., 1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Pimería Alta - Mission Churches of Northern Sonora., undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Pimería Alta - Missions and More., undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Pimería Alta - Natural History., undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Pimería Alta - Review., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Pimería Alta - Smaller Chapters., undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Public Health., 1975 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Public Perception of the Desert in Tucson, Arizona., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Querido Patron., undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Querido Patron., 1900-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Reminiscences of a Franciscan in Papagueria., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Royalty Statement., 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - S-Chuk Shon., 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Santa Ana de Cuiquiburitac., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Santa Cruz and San Agustin., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - The Santa Cruz Trail., undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Schott, Arthur Carl Victor., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Script by Jay Miller for San Xavier TV Movie., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Seasons of War., undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Seasons of War., undated; 1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Sedelmayr – Before Rebellion Draft., 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Sedelmayr – Correspondence., 1981-1994 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Sedelmayr – Illustrations., undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Sedelmayr – Letters., undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Sedelmayr – Place Names Reference List., undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Sedelmayr – Reports undated, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Sedelmayr – Reviews., 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Shenandoah., 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Sierra Pinacate., 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Smoke Signal., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Some Sonoran Missions of Jaliscan Friars., 1969 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Southwest Imagery: A Mugwump Romance., undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Southwest Indian Book – Travel., 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Southwest Parks and Monuments., 1991 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - The Strange Case of the Desert Arsenal, undated; 1959 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Tales from Tiburon – McGee Materials., undated; 1982 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Tarahumara – Annotated Bibliography., undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Tarahumara – Barney Burns notes., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Tarahumara – Bibliographic Materials., undated; 1979 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Tarahumara – Color Proofs., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Tarahumara – Conference of Scholars., undated; 1980 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Tarahumara – Notes from Published Sources., undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Tarahumara – Notes on Material Culture., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Tarahumara – Response Letters., 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Tarahumara – Travel Expenses., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Tarahumara – University of Arizona Edition (1 of 2)., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Tarahumara – University of Arizona Edition (2 of 2)., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Tarahumara – University of Arizona Edition., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Articles., undated; 1909 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Articles by McGee., 1896-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Copyeditor., 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Correspondence., 1901-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Correspondence of Ives and Fontana., 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Finding Aid., 1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Footnotes., 1897 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Full Manuscript., undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Handwriting Deciphering., undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Hinsley McGee Dissertation., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Holographic Copy., undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Introduction., undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Manuscript References., undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Trails to Tiburón – McGee Family Heirs., 1956-1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Notes and Maps., 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Pablo Valencia’s Trial by Thirst., undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Page Proofs., 1999 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Photo Captions., undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Photocopy of Field Diary., undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Photographs., 1959-1999 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Trails to Tiburón – References and Index., undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Ribbon Copy., undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Route Notes., 1895 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Talk., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Trincheras Site., 1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Typescript (1 of 2)., undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Trails to Tiburón – Typescript (2 of 2)., undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Trails to Tiburón - William Dinwiddie and William Johnson., 1961-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Tucson Gas and Electric Company., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Van Dyke Annotated Bibliography., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - The Vikita – A Biblio History., undated; 1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - The Warlike Comanches., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - The Westernmost Skirmish of the Civil War., 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Who Built Mission San Xavier., 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - William Sherley Williams., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 2: Book Reviews
    - A - B., 1968-1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - C – D., 1968-1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - E – H., 1964-1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - I – J., 1964-1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - K – M., 1967-1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - N., 1964-1987 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - O-R, 1959-1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - S., 1969-1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - T – V., 1972-1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - W - Z, 1965-1988 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 3: Theses and Dissertations.
    - Final Papers., undated; 1969 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Fox, Gretchen – Arthur Schott., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Hsu, Dick – Arthur Patterson site., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Williams, Jack – Military Frontier., 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Series III: Correspondence
  Alphabetical. This series contains correspondence and is is organized according to Fontana’s original filing scheme.
  - A – AG., 1962-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - A – ALM., 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - A – AM., 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - A – ARI., 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - A – ARI., 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - A – ARI., 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - A – Arizona O., 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - A – AV, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - AH – AL., 1962-1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Ahlborn, Richard E., 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Ahlborn, Richard E., 1971-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Almaráz, Félix, D. Jr., 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Almaráz, Félix, D. Jr., 1981-1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - ALN – ARI., 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - AM – ARC., ">1972-1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - AN – AZ., 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - ARD – ARL., 1974-1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Arizona Highways., 1979-1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Arizona Highways., 1989-1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Arizona P – AZ., 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - ARJ – BAR., 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - ARJ – BLE., 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - ARJ – BLE., 1998 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - ARJ – BLE., 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - ARM – AZ., 1975-1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - B- BAQ., 1971-1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - B- BD., 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - B- BN., 1956-1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - B- BN., 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bahr, Donald M., 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - BAR – BEA., 1972-1991 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Barnes, Mark., 1973-1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - BAS – BLE., 1990-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - BE – BQ., 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Beatty, Bill and Ethel., undated; 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Beatty, Bill and Ethel., 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Beatty, Bill and Ethel., 1971-1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Beatty, Bill and Ethel., 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - BEB – BEL., 1972-1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - BEM – BEZ., 1971-1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - BF – BN., 1969-1990 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Bleser, Nicholas., 1974-1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Bleser, Nicholas., 1984-1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - BLF – BYR., 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - BLF – COM., 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - BLF – COM., 1998 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - BLF – COM., 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - BO – BQ., 1971-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - BO – BZ., 1956-1962 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - BO – BZ., 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - BR – BRIT., 1971-1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - BR – BZ., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - BRIU – BROW., 1971-1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - BROY – BUF., 1972-1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - BUG – BZ., 1974-1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - BYS – COM., 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - C – CARO., 1971-1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - C – CK., 1955-1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - C – CL., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - C – D., 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Cabat, Erni., 1977-1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - CARP – CART., 1973-1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Carrol, Thomas and Marie Josée., 1976-1991 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - CARU – CHAO., 1971-1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - CHAP – CHIL., 1974-1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cheek, Annetta., 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - CHIN – CL., 1972-1991 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - CL – COQ., 1956-1962 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - CM – COL., 1971-1991 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - CO – CZ., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - CON – COTT., 1971-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - CON – DES., 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - CON – DES., 1995-1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cordry, Dorothy., 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Costo, Jeanette and Rupert., 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - COU – COX., 1972-1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - COY – CRO., 1972-1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - CRU – CZ., 1971-1988 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - CUR – CZ., 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - D., 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - D., 1963-1966 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - D – DEA., 1971-1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - DEB – DEI., 1971-1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - DEM – DIW., 1971-1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - DET – DEW., 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - DET – EWE., 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Dewar, John., 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Dewar, John., 1983-1987 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Dewar, John., 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - DET – EWE., 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - DET – EWE (1 of 2)., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - DET – EWE (2 of 2)., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - DEX – EWE., 1985-1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Dillon, Dick., 1970-1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Dillon, Dick., 1971-1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Dobyns, Henry, 1971-1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Doelle, William., 1977-1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - DON – DZ., 1971-1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - E., 1956-1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - E., 1963-1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - E., 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - EA – ED., 1968-1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - EE – EN., 1972/1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - EP – ES., 1969-1991 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - ESC – EV., 1973-1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Evlar, Robert C., 1970-1988 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - EW – EZ., 1971-1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - EWF – FIZ., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - EWF – GOO., 1971-1995 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - EWF – GOO., 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - F., 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - F – FEL., 1972-1991 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - F – FK., 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - F – FQ., 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - FAG – GOL., 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Fagan, Brian., 1972-1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - FEM – FEZ., 1973-1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - FF – FL., 1971-1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - FJA – GOO., 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - FL – FZ., 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - FO – FOU., 1969-1991 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Fontana, Bernard L., 1955-1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Fontana, Ralph and Jacquie., 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Fontana, Ralph and Jacquie., 1999 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - FOV – FZ., 1971-1990 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - FR – FZ., 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - G., 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - G., 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - G., 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - G – GIK., 1971-1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Gell, Jonathan., 1972-1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - GIL – GOO., 1972-1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Glassie, Henry., 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Glassie, Henry., 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - GOP – GREENL., 1971-1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - GOP – HAL., 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - GOP – HOL., 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - GOP – HOL., 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Green - GZ., 1972-1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - H – HEH., 1956-1962 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - H – HANL., 1969-1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - H – HH., 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - HA – HD., 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Hackenburg, Robert A., 1957-1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Hale, Kenneth L., /1969">1960-1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Hall, Dorothy., 1970-1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - HAM – HOL., 1985-1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - HAN – HARR., 1971-1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Hanlon, Fr. Capistran., 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - HARS – HAY., 1971-1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - HAYD – HAZ., 1979-1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - HE – HER., 1971-1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - HE – HZ., 1961-1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - HEI – HZ., 1956-1962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - HES – HOD., 1960-1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - HI – HZ., 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Hinshaw, Merton., 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Hodge, Gene., 1956-1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - HOE – HOL., 1971-1988 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Hogan, Bro. Lawrence., 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Holterman, Jack., 1971-1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - HOM – JEF., 1979-1995 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - HOM – JEF., 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - HOM – JEF., 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - HOM – JEF., 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - HON – HOW., 1973-1992 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Houlihan, Patrick., 1972-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Houser, John and Nicholas., 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Houser, Nicholas., 1972-1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hoy, William., 1967-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - HS – HUD., 1969-1988 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - HUF – HZ., 1971-1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - I., 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - I., 1967-1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - I - J., 1972-1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Ives, Ronald L., 1956-1962 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - J., 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - J –K., 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - J – JN., 1972-1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - JEG – KAY., 1987-1994 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - JEG – KEL., 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - JEG – KEL., 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Jennings, Francis., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - JOH – JOJ., 1971-1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - JON – JZ., 1972-1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - K., 1956-1962 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - K – KE., 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - K – KELE., 1971-1984 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Kassander, Richard A., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - KAZ – KEL., 1992-1995 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Keleman, Pál., 1985-1992 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Keleman, Pál., 1963-1971 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Keleman, Pál., 1972-1979 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Keleman, Pál., 1980-1982 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Keleman, Pál., 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - KELL – KER., 1970-1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Keller, Robert., 1974-1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - KEM – KUZ., 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - KEM – LUT., 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - KEM – LUT., 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - KEM – LUT., 1998-2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Keneally, Henry J. Jr., 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy, Henry., 1971-1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, Roger., 1980-1992 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - KES – KH., 1971-1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Kessell, John L., 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - KI – KIR., 1974-1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - KI – KZ., 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Kiracofe, James., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - KIS – KZ., 1972-1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Kroeber, Betty., 1980-1987 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Kroeber, Clifton., 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Kroll, Anthony F., 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - KUA – LUT., 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - L., 1956-1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - L., 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - L – LANE., 1972-1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - L – LM., 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - LANF – LEF., 1971-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - LEF – LEZ., 1971-1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - LF – LIO., 1971-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Lindig, Wolfgang., 1965-1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - LIP – LOH., 1972-1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - LOI – LZ., 1971-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Lower, Jeanne and Ray, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - LUV – MOR., 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - LUV- MOR., 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - LUV- MOR., 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - M., 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - M – MANT., 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - M – MANU., 1969-1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - M – MEH., 1956-1962 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - MANU –MD., 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - MANV – MAT., 1971-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - MAU – MC., 1965-1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, Keiran., 1974-1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - McCoy, Robert., 1972-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - McHenry, Paul G., 1971-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - McHenry, Paul G., 1979-1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - MD – ME., 1966-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - MDS – MYR., 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ME – MU., 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - MEI – MZ., 1956-1962 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Merrill, William., 1974-1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Merrill, William., 1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - MF – MIN., 1971-1992 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - MID –MOO., 1968-1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - MOP – MURO., 1970-1991 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - MOS – MZZ., 1995-1998 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - MOS –MZZ., 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - MURP – MZ., 1972-1990 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - MY –MZ., 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Myrick, David., 1967-1970 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Myrick, David., 1971-1979 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Myrick, David., 1980-1984 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Myrick, David., 1985-1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - MYS – ORG., 1990-1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - N., 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - N – NAS., 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - N – O., 1956-1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - N – O., 1967-1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - NAA – ORG., 1993-1998 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - NAA – ORG., 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - NAT – ND., 1971-1992 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - NE – NZ., 1969-1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Neuerberg, Norman., 1977-1992 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Neuerberg, Norman., 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - O., 1961-1966 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - O – OLS., 1971-1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Oklahoma University Press., 1987-1992 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - OLT – OV., 1974-1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Olvera, Jorge., 1967-1970 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - ORH – RAV., 1990-1995 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - ORH – RAV., 1996-1998 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - ORH – RAV., 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - OW – OZ., 1971-1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - P – PARK., 1971-1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - P – PD., 1956-1962 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - P – PN., 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - P – Q., 1967-1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Paloheimo, George and Leonora., 1972-1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - PARL – PEL., 1971-1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - PE – Q., 1962-1965 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - PEN – PET., 1975-1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - PEU – PRA., 1971-1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Pickens, Buford., 1979-1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - PO – Q., 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Polzer, Charles., 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Polzer, Charles., 1967-1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Polzer, Charles., 1971-1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Post Medieval Archaeology., 1968-1969 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark and Fay., 1974-1990 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - PRB – PZ., 1971-1990 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Q., 1974-1991 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - R., 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - R., 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - R – REI., 1972-1992 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - R – RIF., 1956-1962 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Radding de Murrieta, Cynthia., 1972-1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - RAW – ROL., 1990-1995 (Box 35, Folder 25)